(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-12T08:58:17.991820",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub \"Hoshinomi\" - Accepting New Members Now!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY vol.2
[Event: Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub \"Hoshinomi\" - Accepting New Members Now!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY vol.2
[Event: Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星読み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue - (TRACK LIST)
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星読み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub - Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
Pajama Party vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP travelogue
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods
星詠み Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: Hoshiyomi
GUM & DROP
Pajama Party vol.2
Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP travelogue
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods
星詠み Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: Hoshiyomi
星街すいせい Official Fanclub
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
新規会員受付中！
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
PAJAMA PARTY Vol. 2
With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
OITA 2027.2.7 (sun)
OITA - 2027.2.7 (sun)
iichikoグランシアタ
iichiko Grand Theater
開場 17:00 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:00 / Start 18:00
ISHIKAWA 2027.2.20 (sat)
ISHIKAWA - 2027.2.20 (sat)
松任文化会館 ピーノ
Matsuto Bunka Kaikan Piano
開場 17:30 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:30 / Start 18:00
AKITA 2027.2.27 (sat)
AKITA - 2027.2.27 (sat)
あきた芸術劇場ミルハス 中ホール
Akita Arts Theatre Milhas Medium Hall
開場 17:30 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:30 / Start 18:00
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
1st EP travelogue
1st EP - travelogue
2027.2.11 (thu)
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
新規会員受付中！
Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP
好評配信中！
Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event
PAJAMA PARTY Vol. 2
With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
OITA 2027.2.7 (sun)
OITA - 2027.2.7 (sun)
iichikoグランシアタ
iichiko Grand Theater
開場 17:00 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:00 / Start 18:00
ISHIKAWA 2027.2.20 (sat)
ISHIKAWA - 2027.2.20 (sat)
松任文化会館 ピーノ
Matsuto Bunka Kaikan Piano
開場 17:30 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:30 / Start 18:00
AKITA 2027.2.27 (sat)
AKITA - 2027.2.27 (sat)
あきた芸術劇場ミルハス 中ホール
Akita Arts Theatre Milhas Medium Hall
開場 17:30 / 開演 18:00
Doors Open 17:30 / Start 18:00
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
1st EP travelogue
1st EP - travelogue
2027.2.11 (thu)
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRO
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar: Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: New Members Welcome!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Out Now!]
Pajama Party Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar: Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: New Members Welcome!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Out Now!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue
2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Available for Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue
2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
"Once Upon a Stellar" Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimiyomi" Now Accepting New Members!
星街すいせい Official Fanclub
星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
'Hoshimayomi' Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP Now Available!
Pajama Party Vol.2
With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
travelogue
*** (TRACK LIST) ***
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar
- OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub
星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub
'Hoshimayomi' Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP Now Available!
Pajama Party Vol.2
With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
travelogue
*** (TRACK LIST) ***
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRA
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
[Goods Lineup: Once Upon a Stellar]
星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Official Fanclub Recruitment]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Digital Single: GUM & DROP Out Now]
PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2
[Official Event: Pajama Party Vol.2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue
[1st EP: travelogue Track List]
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
[Goods Lineup: Once Upon a Stellar]
星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Official Fanclub Recruitment]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[Digital Single: GUM & DROP Out Now]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol.2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue I
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: "travelogue"]
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official FanClub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fan Club "Hoshiyomi" - Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
["GUM & DROP" Now Available for Streaming!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol.2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue I
[Midnight Grand Orchestra 1st EP: "travelogue"]
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official FanClub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fan Club "Hoshiyomi" - Accepting New Members!]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: Star-Reader New Members Open!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Now Available!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
1ST EP travelogue
2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub: Star-Reader New Members Open!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Now Available!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
1ST EP travelogue
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshiyomi - Now Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Now Available!]
Pajama Party Vol. 2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub Hoshiyomi - Now Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP Now Available!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol.2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Accepting New Members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
"GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol.2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" Accepting New Members!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available!
Pajama Party Vol.2 With Hoshimachi Suisei
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO 2027.2.11 (THU)
(2nd LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRO (Feb 11, 2027)
Once Upon a Stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimyomi" - Now accepting new members!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
GUM & DROP - Now available!
Pajama Party Vol.2 With Hoshimachi Suisei
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRO
[MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO]
Once Upon a stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimonomi" - New Members Welcome!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
["GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!]
PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue *** (TRACK LIST) ***
[MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP "travelogue" - Track List]
2ND LIVE PROJECT ALLEGRO
[MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 2nd LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRO]
Once Upon a stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshimonomi" - New Members Welcome!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
["GUM & DROP" Now Streaming!]
PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2 With HOSHIMACHI SUISEI
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: PAJAMA PARTY Vol.2]
Pajama Party vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
[MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA - 1st EP: travelogue]
2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Accepting New Members!]
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
[GUM & DROP - Now Available!]
Pajama Party vol.2
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event: Pajama Party Vol. 2]
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1st EP travelogue
[MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA - 1st EP: travelogue]
2ND LIVE PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a stellar - OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP -
[Once Upon a Stellar - Official Goods Lineup]
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
[Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub "Hoshiyomi" - Accepting New Members!]
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' - New Members Open!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
'GUM & DROP' - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
(2ND LIVE) PROJECT: ALLEGRIA
Once Upon a Stellar OFFICIAL GOODS LINEUP
Arena Tour 'Once Upon a Stellar' Official Goods Lineup
星街すいせい Official Fanclub 星詠み 新規会員受付中！
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Fanclub 'Hoshiyomi' - New Members Open!
GUM & DROP 好評配信中！
'GUM & DROP' - Now Available!
Hoshimachi Suisei Official Event Pajama Party vol. 2
MIDNIGHT GRAND ORCHESTRA 1ST EP travelogue (TRACK LIST)
Once Upon a Stellar
本日はご来場いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending today.
まもなく開演となりますので、お座席でお待ちください。
The show will begin shortly, so please take your seats.
会場内の注意事項についてご案内いたします。
We would like to make some announcements regarding venue rules.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
また本日は混雑が予想されますため
Also, as congestion is expected today,
開場予定時刻より前倒しして
we may begin guiding you in ahead
ご案内を始める場合がございます
of the scheduled opening time.
また開場後は混雑が予想されますため
Furthermore, as congestion is expected after the doors open,
速やかにご自席の方へお戻りください
please return to your seats promptly.
お連れ様がいらっしゃるお客様におかれましては
For customers who have companions joining them,
お手元にチケットをお持ちの上
please have your tickets ready
お待ち合わせいただけますよう
so you can meet up with them smoothly.
お願い申し上げます
Thank you for your cooperation.
皆様 まもなく開場時刻を迎えます
Ladies and gentlemen, the doors will open shortly.
お手持ちのチケットをご確認の上
Please check your tickets,
あらかじめご入場列にお並びください
and line up in the entrance queue in advance.
あ、そうの星し！
Ah, that star!
もうちょっと右しゅいな。
A little more to the right, sui!
あ、もっと左しゅいな。
Ah, a little more to the left, sui!
あ、そうそうそうそう！
Ah, right, right, right, right!
いい感じしゅいねー！
Looking good, sui!
じゃ、スイッチ
Now, switch...
オン！
On!
おー！
Oooh!
みんな、ヤッホー！
Everyone, hello!
すいちゃんしゅい！
It's Sui-chan, sui!
よー！
Yay!
星読みのみんな、今日が初めてのみんな、
All Hoshiyomi, everyone here for the first time today,
会いに来てくれて、ありがとうしゅい！
thank you for coming to meet me, sui!
いや、もうすぐ始まるんだけど、その前に！
Well, it's about to start, but before that!
よいしょ！
Heave-ho!
ライブマナーズ！
Live Manners!
ということで、すいちゃんからみんなへ、ライブを楽しむためのお願いごとが３つあるしゅい！
With that, Sui-chan has three requests for everyone to enjoy the live concert, sui!
まず、ひとつめ！
First one!
ライブ中は撮影録音は
During the live concert, taking photos and recordings
できないしゅいよ！
are not allowed, sui!
今日しか見られない景色、一緒に楽しもうしゅい！
Let's enjoy the scenery you can only see today together, sui!
次、ふたつめ！
Next, second one!
応援してくれるのはすごく嬉しいしゅい！
It makes me so happy when you cheer for me, sui!
でも、周りがみえなくなると
But if you lose sight of your surroundings...
すいちゃーん！今日が一番！
Sui-chan! Today is the best!
すいちゃーん！すいちゃーん！
Sui-chan! Sui-chan!
すいちゃーん！すいちゃーん！今日が一番可愛いよー！
Sui-chan! Sui-chan! Today is the cutest!
ということで、周りがびっくりしちゃうような大声やコールはダメしゅい！
That means, loud voices or calls that startle those around you are a no-go, sui!
あと、「すいちゃん今日もかわいい！」コールは、すいちゃんが合図するまで取っておいてしゅいよ！
Also, save the "Sui-chan is cute today too!" call until Sui-chan gives the cue, sui!
そして、みっつめ！
And third!
みんなペンライト持ってるしゅいかー？
Does everyone have a penlight, sui?
見せて見せてー！
Show me, show me!
ライブが始まったらもっとすごくなるしゅいね！
When the live starts, it'll get even more amazing, sui!
でも、使うときにはルールがあるしゅい！
But there are rules when using them, sui!
改造ペンライトや、26cmを超えるもの、高輝度タイプは使っちゃダメしゅい！
Modified penlights, ones over 26cm, and high-brightness types are forbidden, sui!
みんなでルールを守って楽しいライブにするしゅいよ！協力してくれるしゅいかー？
Let's all follow the rules and make it a fun live! Will you cooperate, sui?
じゃあ、一回みんなでペンライト消すしゅい！
Then, everyone turn off your penlights once, sui!
せーの！完璧！ありがとー！
Ready, go! Perfect! Thank you!
よし、これで準備OK！みんなもいけるしゅいかー？
Alright, preparation OK! Can everyone do it too, sui?
それじゃあ…始まるしゅい！
Well then... it's starting, sui!
昔々、きらきらと光る、
Long, long ago, sparkling brightly,
不思議なお城に、
in a mysterious castle,
星街すい星という女の子が住んでいました。
a girl named Hoshimachi Suisei lived.
そこはまるで、おとぎ話の絵本から飛び出してきたような、素敵なお城です。
It was a wonderful castle, just like something that jumped out of a fairy tale book.
夜になると、すい星は窓辺で歌を歌います。
When night falls, Suisei sings songs by the window.
ご覧 手を少し伸ばし
Look, if you stretch out your hand just a little,
すれ違う二人 その先はさ
what lies ahead for the two of us passing by...
人混み目立った その心
That heart standing out in the crowd,
僕が誰ばあくでしょ
who could it be?
譲れないわマイセルフ
I won't compromise my self,
邪魔しないでメイクアップステージさ
don't get in my way on this makeup stage!
どこでそちら どちら様ですか
Where are you? Who on earth are you?
もう1点ですか
Is that another point?
仕舞って大変だわ
Putting it away is a hassle!
ポップノイズを消して 目と目 そらさないでね
Erase the pop noise, don't look away from my eyes!
巡り合うんだ どんな歴史にももううんざりだわ
We keep meeting, I'm already sick of any history!
集めはあとミュージカル アビトースボウイ
Collect them later, musical habit-loose boy!
たとえどんな闇も ごめん 遊ばせ
No matter what darkness comes, excuse me!
モルモット ガルガル ボウ
Guinea pig, roar, roar, boy!
ノーモアタイム ファックアップバイト
No more time, fuck up bite!
ああ 少々です ありがとう どうぞお遊びレッツゴー
Ah, just a moment, thanks, go ahead and play, let's go!
知ってネタ見そで見からやがみに 暇なんですか
Knowing the punchline and peeking, are you free?
誰をも添えては殺す ご機嫌よ
Accompanying and killing whoever it is, how are you?
ロット ブラッシュを浴びて 耳を離さないでね
Bathe in the lot brush, don't let go of my ears!
巡り合うんだ どんな言い訳も今壊せたわ
We meet again, I've smashed any excuses now!
集めはあとミュージカル アビトースボウイ
Collect them later, musical habit-loose boy!
ああ、イェイ、イェイ、イェイ
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
感じて 止まらぬ悪のように飛び込む 世界は回る
Feel it, jumping into a world like unstoppable evil, it spins round and round.
人見知る終わりに続く ストーリー ひとりの１０マイル トゥーミー 輝け
Continuing to the end of shyness, a story of a solo 10 miles to me, shine on!
ふたりはどんな今も 高く舞い上げたわ
No matter what kind of present the two of us have, we soared it high.
集めはあとミュージカル アビトースボウイ
Collect them later, musical habit-loose boy!
たとえどんなエンディング待ち受けてても
No matter what kind of ending awaits us,
モルモット ガルガル ボウ 進め
Guinea pig, roar, roar, boy, move forward!
きっと覚めない心 覚めない夢 パーフェクトショーなんかじゃない
A heart that will never wake up, a dream that won't wake up, it's not some perfect show!
どこで誰か 笑っても ごめん遊ばせ
Even if someone laughs somewhere, excuse me!
ノーモアタイム ファックアップバイト
No more time, fuck up bite!
まだ見ぬ記憶流れ ワールドワイド
Flowing into unseen memories, worldwide!
発見さーち こだわりやがって わお
Discovery search, being so picky, wow!
ハッピーバースデイ イェイ
Happy birthday, yeah!
この今だけの知恵 投げ捨てるネクストエピソード
Wisdom for this moment alone, throwing away the next episode.
旅人ナアジ にても漏れぬ 歪んだ顔を べったりさせない 予想できない
Traveler's refuge, leaking everywhere, don't make your distorted face stick, it's unpredictable!
ワッツアップ バイバイ ランララ
What's up, bye-bye, la-la-la!
シンフォニー チューフォ とっておきのトリート 期待して
Symphony, choose for, expect a special treat!
時計の針よりも 早いのさ
Faster than the hands of a clock,
ワンダースウィートライフ
Wonder sweet life!
サーストカミング 寒空みたいな
Thirst coming, like a cold winter sky,
ソウアイキャンビー 足りないよ
So I can be, I'm still not satisfied!
ドウシュガーフリー これ以上ないね
Do sugar-free, it doesn't get better than this!
エイエイ アウトオブコントロール
Hey, hey, out of control!
狂い鳴れよ カミカミ 急にヤミヤミ 中揺れるよ カミカミ
Madness ringing, bite-bite, suddenly darkness-darkness, swaying in the middle, bite-bite!
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
狂おしいほど
So passionately
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
Let me give you some...
ささやかな 私の道
My humble path
そこここから まわれ右
Turn around from right here
But I want to give you what you want
You're the one that's spice and what you need
I'm a hooky chan and you are the champion
You're addicted, see the big show
See the big show
ドルチェキの treatment
Dolce treatment
させてって
Let me do it
華やぐ日々をさせて
Let me live glamorous days
瞳の火は絶やさないで
Don't let the fire in your eyes go out
さあさ
Now then
神々見たいね
I want to see the gods
想像力じゃ足りないよ
Imagination isn't enough
I want you go free
これ以上ないね
There's nothing more than this
永遠アウトもよく今日
Forever, out is fine too today
So sparkle on
Every moment with us
Play your heart out like a cherry cola
その夜は煌めいて darling
That night sparkles, darling
永遠なんて信じないわ
I don't believe in eternity
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
Jewel in the... 狂おしいほど
Jewel in the... So passionately
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
Jewel in the... しがみつくのよ
Jewel in the... Cling to it
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
Jewel in the... 狂おしいほど
Jewel in the... So passionately
Jewel in the... 鏡よ鏡
Jewel in the... Magic mirror
Jewel in the... Let me give you some...
ささやかな 私の道
My humble path
そこここから まわれ右
Turn around from right here
But I want to give you what you want
You're the one that's spice
I'm a hooky chan and you are the champion
You're addicted, see the big show
さあ、始めようか
Now then, shall we begin?
こぼれ落ちる感情が 歪んで溢れてたぁ
Overflowing emotions were distorting
茶番な愛嬌の この衝動が
Farcical charm, this impulse
You wanna kiss for free bye-bye
あなたの目に映る可愛いわたし
The cute me reflected in your eyes
この瞬間を凌いでみたいの 壊れるまで
I want to try surviving this moment until it breaks
ノーワンスは殺した 神話聞かせて 今だけはアモレカロレ 夜に甘えて
No one killed it, tell me the myth
踏み口づけに意味なんてないの 抑えられない呪詛で
Stepping into a kiss has no meaning with an uncontrollable curse
わたしの思う愛情が 滲んでよごれてたぁ
My affection bled and became soiled
矛盾に逆らったような 過剰な呪文
Like going against contradiction, an excessive spell
Bye-bye 大きくなったって愛なんて知らないわ
Bye-bye, even if it grows big, I don't know about love
この瞬間を誤魔化してみない 壊れるまで
Why don't we try deceiving this moment until it breaks?
狂おしいの世界は 妖しくきらめいていて
The mad world is mesmerizing and sparkling
こんなどこのもませたら ねえこのまま連れ出してくれない
If I make someone drink this somewhere... hey, won't you take me away?
探して見させて この先も迷って迷って 黒目を縫合せて
Search and let me see, getting lost and lost ahead, sewing up my pupils
ダメこのままじゃ 浮かんでで たりないよ You wanna kiss for free
No, not like this, floating... it's not enough, you wanna kiss for free
これ以上ないね 永遠におぼれて おしまい
There's nothing more than this, drowning eternally, the end
あの頃夢見た僕らは 絵空事ではなくて
The dreams we dreamed back then were no mere fantasy,
答えのない物語を 偶像にしていくのさ
turning a story without answers into our idol.
たとえ遠回りをしたとしても
Even if we take the long way around,
必ず僕ら この手で掴むよ
we will surely grasp it with our own hands.
あの場所で輝く星に
To the star shining in that place,
いつかたどり着くことを信じて
believing we'll reach it someday.
怖がる事なんてないよ
There's nothing to be afraid of;
明日への希望となり
it becomes our hope for tomorrow.
悲しみは歌で包むよ
We'll wrap our sorrows in song,
同じ空見る僕らが居るから
because we share the same sky.
君とこれから歩むのさ
Walking forward from now on with you,
届けよう この声に乗せて
let's let it reach us, carried on this voice.
青く澄んだ遥かな空 漂う雲はすり抜けて
Slipping through the clouds in the clear, blue, distant sky,
形持たない不確実さ 胸に宿る確信
formless uncertainty, a conviction dwelling in our hearts.
諦めそうなときにいつも 包んでくれた 人の優しさが
The kindness of others that always embraced me when I was about to give up
この空の果てまで広がる 大きな愛で伝え続けよう
I'll keep conveying with a great love extending to the edge of this sky.
限りある旅の道中で 後悔しない道を
On this finite journey, choosing a path without regrets,
どれだけの時が経っても 変わらないものは胸ここにあるから
no matter how much time passes, what remains unchanged is right here in my heart.
強く信じ 未来を描いて
Strongly believing, drawing the future,
このまま 夢のその先へ
onward like this, beyond the dream.
僕らの目指す 遥か彼方へ
Toward the distant horizon we aim for,
そびえ立つ階段 走り出すだけ
just start running up the towering stairs.
この身果てまで 全て命がけ
Until this body perishes, risking everything,
涙を笑顔に変えるため
to turn tears into smiles.
そう 世界中の人を敵にしても
Yes, even if we make the whole world our enemy,
僕らはずっと君の味方だよ
we will always be on your side.
だから大丈夫 振り返らず行こう
So it's okay, let's move forward without looking back,
たどり着くところで笑おう
and smile when we reach our destination.
心が打ち砕かれても
Even if our hearts are shattered,
隣にいつも僕らが居るから
we will always be right beside you.
巡り合えた 軌跡とともに
Along with the trajectory of our meeting,
ここから今始まる
it all begins right here and now.
悲しみは歌で包むよ
We'll wrap our sorrows in song,
同じ空見る僕らが居るから
because we share the same sky.
君とこれから歩むのさ
Walking forward from now on with you,
届けよう この声に乗せて
let's let it reach us, carried on this voice.
巡り合えた 軌跡とともに
Along with the trajectory of our meeting,
ここから今始まる
it all begins right here and now.
あの頃夢見た僕らは 絵空事ではなくて
The dreams we dreamed back then were no mere fantasy,
答えのない物語を 偶像にしていくのさ
turning a story without answers into our idol.
たとえ遠回りをしたとしても
Even if we take the long way around,
必ず僕ら この手で掴むよ
we will surely grasp it with our own hands.
あの場所で輝く星に
To the star shining in that place,
いつかたどり着くことを信じて
believing we'll reach it someday.
怖がる事なんてないよ 明日への希望となり
There's nothing to be afraid of; it becomes our hope for tomorrow.
悲しみは歌で包むよ
We'll wrap our sorrows in song,
同じ空見る僕らが居るから
because we share the same sky.
君とこれから歩むのさ
Walking forward from now on with you,
届けよう この声に乗せて
let's let it reach us, carried on this voice.
始まり聖生「アリナツア2026 ワンズ アポン ア ステラ」へ、ようこそ！
Welcome to Hoshimachi Suisei's 'ARIA TOUR 2026: Once Upon a Stella'!
この城すごくない？
Isn't this castle amazing?
あの、1日目も来ましたって人？
Um, anyone here who also came on Day 1?
え、2日目から来ました、今日から来ましたって人？
Um, anyone who came from Day 2? Or came starting today?
え、じゃあ2日目から来た人は、びっくりしたよね？
Wait, so those who came from Day 2 must have been surprised, right?
そう、あの、物販で販売してました絵本
Yes, um, the picture book sold at the merch booth,
『ワンズ アポン ア ステラ』、時をかける水星のお城の世界観・物語を舞台に、こういうお城を建てさせていただきまして、え、スタジオセトラチーム……
'Once Upon a Stella'—set in the world of Suisei's Castle Through Time, we had this castle built, and um, Studio Setra team...
ライブ制作チームの皆さんと一緒にね、
Along with the live production team,
この美術、演出こだわって使わせていただきました！
we've really put our hearts into this art and staging!
拍手！
Let's hear it!
あの、ま、Day1に来てた人もいっぱいいるということで
Um, well, I'm sure a lot of you were here for Day 1 as well,
あの、Day1では、このお城のすごいところ
and on Day 1, I talked about how amazing this castle is—
この上の丸い
this round thing up here—
アストロラーベと呼ばれるなんだっけ？星座盤みたいな、星図盤みたいなやつが
what was it called? An astrolabe? Like a celestial chart, or a star map or something—
すごいよって話をしたんですけど、
I talked about how incredible that is.
え、覚えてますかDay1来た人？
Do you remember, everyone who came to Day 1?
Day2の人も覚えてるよって今言ったよね絶対。
And Day 2 folks are definitely thinking, "I remember too!" right now.
え、じゃあちょっと、そうだよね、ちょっと違うこと言うならば、あの、バンドさんがお城の上に立ってる。
Um, well, right, if I were to say something a bit different—look, the band members are standing up on top of the castle!
すごっ！すごい！
Isn't that amazing? Incredible!
そうだよね。
Right?
はい、あのいつものバンドメンバーでお送りしております。皆さんよろしくお願いしますね。
Yes, we're performing with my usual band members. Everyone, please give them a warm welcome!
はい、ええ、スタジオステラ設立して初めてのソロライブということで
Yes, um, since this is our very first solo live concert since establishing Studio Stellar,
私もこだわりにしてこだわり抜いてね、もう毎日のように、あのスタッフさんと
I've been extremely particular about every single detail, meeting with the staff almost every day—
「スイちゃん、これ監修して」「これもちょうだい」「これはもっとこう…」本当により頑張って作ったんで、
"Suisei-chan, please supervise this." "Suisei-chan, supervise this too." "This should be more like this..." We really worked super hard on all of it!
ぜひ最後までこのライブを楽しみ尽くしてください！
Please enjoy and make the most of this concert all the way to the end!
昨日と違うことがあります。それは……配信を見てるみんなーー！
There's one thing different from yesterday. And that is... everyone watching the stream!
ちょっとあのここらへんにコメントの雨が…いぇーい！うおお！見てるよ！はーい！ふー、見てる？スイちゃん、
There's a rain of comments right around here... Yay! Woo! We see you! Hi! Woo, are you watching? Suisei-chan,
っていうね、声が、はい、あります。
we can hear you saying, yes.
楽しめているようです。YouTubeはね、あの途中までしか観れませんので
It looks like you're having fun. Since YouTube only streams part of the show,
ライブを最後まで見たい方は概要欄のSPWN、Z-anで配信チケットをゲットしてください。
if you want to watch the live stream all the way to the end, please grab a ticket on SPWN or Z-an via the description box!
え、なんとねでもね、いつもだったらここで「なんとかごめんなさい、ここでチラ見せは終了」って言うじゃないですか。なんと今日はここで終わらない！
But wait, usually around this time I'd say, "Sorry everyone, that's it for the preview!" But guess what? We're not ending here today!
じゃあどこで終わるのか、ちょっとDay1来た人はね、ここじゃねって予想しながらね、見てください。
So where will it end? For those who came to Day 1, try guessing "Is it here?" as you watch!
ということで、ちょっとお忘れじゃないですか？これの、あれ！やっちゃいますよ！アリーナの皆さん、行けますか？
With that said, aren't you forgetting something? We're gonna do *that* song! Arena, are you ready?
レベル3の皆さん、行けますか？
Level 3, are you ready?
レベル5の皆さん、行けますか？
Level 5, are you ready?
レベル7の人、行けるんですか？
Level 7, can you do it?
遠いなとか思ってんでしょ？レベル7もレベル5もレベル3もね、アリーナの後ろも見えてますからね！
You think you're too far away, right? Level 7, Level 5, Level 3, even the back of the arena—I can see all of you!
気合い入れちゃいますよ！
Let's get fired up!
あ、配信のみんなも、行けるー！
Ah, everyone on the stream too, can you do it?!
ありがとうございます、配信の皆さんの分も。
Thank you, including for everyone on the stream.
それでは、水星のごとく現れたあの日、あの星待つ水星です！
And now, as if appearing like Mercury that day... Hoshimachi Suisei!
スイちゃん、うわーー！
Suisei-chan, woo!
まだいけるな。え？ ちょっと今日みんな雨降ったから冷やられちゃってんじゃないの？ねえ。
We can still keep going. Huh? Did you guys catch a chill today because it rained? Hey.
吹き飛ばそう。ね？この湿気吹き飛ばそう。もっかい行くよ。
Let's blow it away. Right? Let's blow away this humidity. Let's go again.
スイちゃんはーー！いけるやないのーー！
Suisei-chan is—! You guys can totally do it!
この後も最後まで喉涸らしていってくださいね！
Keep shouting until your throats are hoarse right to the very end!
Once Upon a Starの物語はまだまだ始まったばかりです
The story of "Once Upon a Star" has only just begun.
みんな最後までついてきてください
Please stay with me all the way to the end.
それでは次の曲に行きたいと思います。聴いてください。
Now, I'd like to move on to the next song. Please listen.
光がひとつ 灯ったと思った
I thought a single light had flickered on,
天を彩った秒針が綺麗だ
and the second hand ornamenting the heavens was so lovely.
僕の吐いた白い煙より消してしまえたらな
If only I could just erase it along with the white smoke I exhaled...
押し殺して深く沈んだ
Muffled and sinking deep down,
泣き声さえ聴いているから
because it hears even my stifled cries,
君をさした不穏な靴も
even the ominous shoes that pointed at you,
僕の顎を拾って塗り潰して全部みだりになって
picking up my chin, painting over it all, becoming disorderly...
星の海を流れていった
drifted away into the sea of stars.
果てしない闇の中にそっと歯を添えたならほら
If I gently bared my teeth into the endless darkness, look...
彗星が僕の背中を伝った
A comet traced down my back.
誰もいない夜の空を詰めた
Packing the empty night sky,
深く沈んだ街の中へ
into the deeply sunken town,
降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
whose sorrow is it that pours down?
星はまた遠くへ描いて飛んだ 昏く濁った思考を回して
Stars trace far away again and fly, spinning dark, muddy thoughts,
いつでも帰れるなんて言えなかった 欲しいがった後の私
I couldn't say I could always go back; that's me after wanting it so much.
孤独を積んだガランドの空も
Even the empty sky loaded with solitude
置き去りにした音のように
like a sound left behind
君をさした不穏な靴も
even the ominous shoes that pointed at you
僕の顎を拾って塗り潰して
picking up my chin, painting over it all,
君の指輪を沿った
following your ring,
星の海に立ち止まった
stopping in the sea of stars.
押し退るその光が誰かをまた救うとな
If that pushing light saves someone once more,
彗星が僕らの名を並べた
a comet lined up our names.
この空をずっと君にあげる 生き残った言葉の重みを引っ提げて
I'll give you this sky forever, carrying the weight of surviving words,
降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
whose sorrow is it that pours down?
星はまた遠くへ描いて飛んだ
Stars trace far away again and fly,
無秩序の視線がバイザルように
so that the disorderly gaze bypasses us...
君とまた会えるから エロスから 僕はどうか
because I can meet you again, from eros, how am I—
星の名前をひとつ見つけても
even if I find a single star's name?
悲しみが溢れそうになること 天球で離れれば離れても
Becoming on the verge of overflowing with sorrow, even if separated far across the celestial sphere,
僕らは繋がっているから
we are connected.
彗星が僕ら上を飛んだ
A comet flew above us,
誰もいない夜の空を詰めた
packing the empty night sky.
深く沈んだ街の中へ
Into the deeply sunken town,
降り注ぐのは誰の悲しみだろう
whose sorrow is it that pours down?
星はまた遠くへ描いて飛んだ 無秩序の視線がバイザルように
Stars trace far away again and fly, so that the disorderly gaze bypasses us,
いつでも帰れるなんて言えなかった
I couldn't say I could always go back.
星が降ったあとの待つ
Waiting after the stars fell,
僕はもうずっと君の行方を探し続けてた
I've kept searching for your whereabouts all this time.
孤独なファンタジー 寂しがりぞめぞめ
A lonely fantasy, lonely and restless,
今のままで孤独にとらまる衝動
an impulse to be caught in solitude just as I am.
星屑の言葉を知りたいだけ
I just want to know the words of stardust.
本当はね、あなたが好き
Actually, I love you,
最低なことを言っちゃってごめんね
I'm sorry for saying such awful things.
ちょっとだけ素直になれない言い訳は
Excuses for not being a bit more honest
いらない 意味ない 君はどこ？
are unnecessary, meaningless. Where are you?
好きを失ったみたいな
Like I've lost my love,
心はどこへたどり着いて
where does my heart end up?
おんなじことばかり繰り返して
Repeating the exact same things over and over,
それがこの僕らで踊るの
that's how we dance, just the two of us.
バカが独り作り上げるまで泣き喚き叫んで消えないように
Crying and screaming until a fool builds it alone so it won't fade,
魔法みたいなすごい魔法の様な主人公なら
if I were a protagonist in a magical, amazing story—
小説結末最後はとなってまハッピーエンド
even if the novel's ending turns out to be a happy one,
するなら好きにさせてよ大人になってもいいや
let me do as I please, it's fine even if I grow up.
真っさかさまに堕ちて痛む重力みんなと引き込もう
Falling headfirst into painful gravity, dragging everyone in.
秘密の夜が交わって遠くへ行こう
Let's cross through secret nights and go far away.
息絶える最後で行い真っ直ぐな人生よりも
Rather than a straight life ending in our final breath,
文字に合う星に恋焦がれて
yearning for the star that matches our letters,
月が綺麗だななんてこの世はすべて終わったアリホッサ
whispering 'the moon is beautiful,' as if this world has ended entirely.
本当はね、どんなに揺るいでる
Actually, no matter how shaken I am,
君の瞳の奥へと
deep into your eyes,
見つめ合ってフォーカス
focusing as we gaze at each other.
退屈な日々の真実の素顔なんて
The true face of boring days,
なんだかんだわかんないから
we never really figure out anyway,
もっともっともっともっともっと、
so more, more, more, more, more—
バカって言われて空っぽ空だけだつように
like being called a fool leaves just an empty sky,
貼り付きたい諦めちゃってはもうあどうえんでん
wanting to cling on, giving up is already a dead end,
だけど私の勇気をもうどうなったっていいや
but my courage, it's fine no matter what happens now.
火花みたいに燃えた私
Burning like sparks, I
いつも日課忘れてちゃった
always forgot my daily routine.
泣かないでなんて感情の縛り
Constraints of emotion like 'don't cry',
挟んで特別になんだおう
squeezed in to become special.
また手を取りかきなくされて聖者とエライトいこう
Holding hands again, losing our way, let's go with the saint.
変わり感じる距離まで引き寄せて
Pulling close to the distance we feel,
月の涙が降ったこの世はまるで
tears of the moon fell upon this world,
ストレンジャー愛を避けて
like a stranger avoiding love.
まっさかさまに堕ちて痛む重力みんなと引き込もう
Falling headfirst into painful gravity, dragging everyone in.
秘密の夜が交わって遠くへ行こう
Let's cross through secret nights and go far away.
息絶える最後で行い真っ直ぐな人生よりも
Rather than a straight life ending in our final breath,
文字に合う星に恋焦がれて
yearning for the star that matches our letters,
月が綺麗だななんてこの世はすべて終わったアイホッサ
whispering 'the moon is beautiful,' as if this world has ended entirely.
私いつも勇気が足りないから自分を大切にできないんだ
I always lack courage, so I can't cherish myself.
痛みを見ないと気づけやしないんだ
Unless I look at the pain, I never realize it.
ああ今日もカラメルペイン
Ah, caramel pain today as well.
引っこねなんか見られないよだって
I can't be seen moving out, because
世界もこんなにも僕最小服装で歩きたくれないし
the world is like this and I don't want to walk in minimal clothes either,
甘えて頭痛いし
pampered and with a headache,
本当へたでただようだけの24/7
clumsily drifting 24/7.
ほいていくよ、ほいていくよ、今までは手にしたものはすべてものさいるも
Throwing it away, everything I've held onto until now...
加われちゃっても今がいいよだって私私の中のままずっといたいんだもん
even if I get caught, right now is fine, because I want to stay as my true self.
ルートフールどうでもいいよデッドセメストもっと危ないことしなきゃ勝ちなんでしょ
Root fool, whatever, dead semester, if you don't do dangerous things you can't win, right?
何を犠牲にだってしょうがないんだよ
It can't be helped whatever we sacrifice.
今までこの胸の痛みだけ抱いて
Holding only this chest pain until now,
リフィールみたいに剥ぐなこうしたっていつかバレちゃうよ
don't peel it off like a refill, it'll get exposed someday.
見たいとか話すのもうに君に言ってんのは変わんない変わんないな
Talking about wanting to see you, what I'm telling you hasn't changed at all.
好きのハニメも
Even the honeyed pain of love...
忘れちゃうし
"I'll just forget you,"
次の人なんて
"And the next person,"
いなくなっちゃうんだ
"will just vanish,"
サヨナラ
"goodbye."
決定的なことは
"The definitive thing is"
いつまでも続けさ
"that it goes on forever."
もう後悔しないように前を向いてできるということ
"That I can look ahead without any regrets,"
放っておいていくよ
"Just leave me be,"
"just leave me be,"
放っておいていくよ
"just leave me be."
爪先立ちしてイデオロギーもスタイルも
"Standing on tiptoe, my ideology and style"
汚れてたって気にしないよ
"Even if they're stained, I don't care,"
だっで私 私に恋してみたいんだもんね
"Because I want to fall in love with myself, right?"
愛してるよ
"I love you,"
愛してるよ サヨナラ
"I love you, goodbye."
なんて涙が流れちゃうけど
"Though tears keep falling like this,"
何を犠牲にしたってしょうがないんだよ
"It can't be helped, no matter what I sacrifice."
この胸の痛みだけ
"Only the pain in this chest..."
大丈夫
"It's okay."
今日も空振る Pain
"Today too, a swinging-and-missing pain,"
ねぇ 私には雪が足りないんだから
"Hey, since I don't have enough snow,"
自分を大切にできないんだ
"I can't cherish myself."
少しが鳴すんだ
"I'll ring it a little."
今日も空振る Pain
"Today too, a swinging-and-missing pain,"
冒頭無料配信は終了いたしました。
The free opening stream has ended.
配信チケットは概要欄から！
Check the description for streaming tickets!